[theme music]
Michelle, you wanna help daddy
separate the laundry?
- I'm not busy.
- Okay.
Everything red, green, yellow
or bright color
goes in this pile
and everything white
goes in this pile.
You got it?
Got it, dude.
White.
Green.
Red.
Oh, no, Michelle.
No food in the laundry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, honey,
it's not your fault.
Daddy didn't explain it right.
I was a bad boy.
Go to your room.
Okay, but will
you come with me?
I'm not busy.
[instrumental music]
[Jesse Frederick singing
"Everywhere You Look"]
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ What ever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milk man
the paper boy ♪
♪ Evenin' TV ♪
♪ How did I get
to living here ♪
♪ Somebody tell me please ♪
♪ This old world's ♪
♪ Confusing me ♪
♪ Clouds as mean
as you ever seen ♪
♪ Ain't a bird
who knows your tune ♪
♪ Then a little voice ♪
♪ Inside you whispers ♪
♪ Kid don't sell
your dreams so soon ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold onto ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a place ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waiting ♪
♪ To carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Hi, Michelle.
[whistling]
[barking]
Oh, isn't that nice?
Your doggy said hello.
No, that was me.
Danny, you're not
driving me to the DMV.
You drive like
a little old lady.
- I'm taking my motorcycle.
- Oh, no, you're not.
Your driver's license
expired two months ago.
So I forgot to renew it.
I can get away with one
more drive down to the DMV.
Jesse, the law is the law.
Don't make me
take away your keys.
I hope you never
get any real power.
Michelle, keep an eye
on Joey for me.
Look at this, Michelle.
"Psychic hit by lightning."
[laughing]
Boy, if he was any good,
he would have seen that comin'.
Michelle, did you eat
my peanut butter sandwich?
Doggy ate it.
Now, you know that's not true.
Now, where did you hide it?
The doggy ate it.
Now, I know
the doggy didn't eat it
'cause I can see
inside his tummy.
Joey.
Whoa! There's a dog
in our yard.
I told you so.
Hey there, little guy.
What are you doing here?
Oh, like the dog's
gonna answer me.
Are you friendly?
Oh, that's sweet.
Oh, that's wet.
Oh, that's enough.
Oh, your tag says
you've had all your shots
and your name is Minnie.
Hi, Minnie.
Can you shake hands?
Look.
[gasps]
There's a dog in our yard.
We got a dog!
It is our dog, isn't it?
It's in our yard,
so it must be our dog.
We got a dog!
Steph, Minnie is not our dog.
Her tag says she's from Ohio?
Where's Ohio?
Well, it's up the street,
about 2000 miles.
And she came all this way
just to live with us.
Well, it was worth the trip.
You're gonna love it here.
Come on, Minnie,
I'll show you around.
Uh, Steph..
Come on in, Minnie.
But wipe your feet first.
Dad is gonna love you.
This is the kitchen.
We'll set an extra plate
for you tonight.
Come on, I'll show
you your new room.
Steph, Steph, we gotta talk.
This is my sister
Michelle's room.
This is the bathroom.
In case you need it.
No, Minnie,
that's Uncle Jesse's room.
Uh, Minnie, that is not
a good place to hang out.
I'll be right back, Michelle.
Steph, what is the dog
doing on Jesse's bed?
Joey, she's come 2000 miles.
Her feet are tired.
Hi, I'm back from school.
I'm going over to Kimmy's.
That's a dog, right?
This is our new dog, Minnie.
She's from Ohio.
(D.J.)
'Come here, girl.'
Hi, Minnie.
Oh, oh, look, she loves to hug.
Oh, she's a Tanner already.
Girls, I love the dog
as much as you do
but we can't keep her.
How can you say this?
- Don't you want a dog?
- Well, of course, I do.
I've wanted
a dog my whole life
but this dog
already has an owner.
But if the owner
doesn't want her
we can keep her, right?
Well, personally,
I would love that
but your dad
may feel differently.
Then, let's not tell him.
What're you gonna do?
Stick a dress on her and pretend
she's a new friend from school?
Works for me.
Come on, let's all
take a nap together.
Hi, Minnie.
[instrumental music]
[door opens]
Hey, Joey.
What are you doing
with that bowl of water?
Uh, I'm very thirsty.
Ah!
Did you get
your driver's license?
Do not ask me about
my written test, capisci?
Capisci.
So, Danny, what happened
with Jesse's written test?
Well, he got his name right
and most of his address.
I mean, why do they ask
such idiotic questions?
Nobody knows how far
you're supposed to park
from a railroad track.
(together)
Seven and a half feet.
Okay, two people know.
I'm gonna get back there
tomorrow and ace that test.
I can't believe I failed.
How'd you pass
the test the last time?
Well, I might've
accidentally caught a glimpse
of my neighbor's paper.
This time, they passed out
different tests
to everyone in room.
It's like, they don't
trust us or something.
I don't get it.
I drive the freeways.
They give every
idiot in the world
a driver's license.
Not every idiot.
Look at this,
I'm taking lip from a guy
who still chews
Flintstones vitamins, look out.
Joey, what did dad say
about...you know who?
I haven't talked to him yet.
(together)
Bye.
Hold it.
Okay, what's going on
and how much is it
gonna cost me?
You know, dad,
we've been thinking.
What we need around here
is someone from..
...maybe, Ohio.
Well, maybe we do
need someone from Ohio..
...but I'd like
to hear more about this
before I go ahead
and order one.
Michelle, I know
you're in there.
Come on out, Michelle.
Okay, young lady
I'm gonna come in there
and get you.
I'm gonna come in and get you.
[Jesse screaming]
What are you doin' here?
[barking]
Where did you come from?
A likely story.
Get out!
Hey, you better fix it.
(Jesse)
'Where are you,
you mangy mutt?'
Uh-oh, trouble.
Go under the bed.
Hurry!
Alright, dog.
I know you're in here.
Come out with your paws up.
No doggy here.
[barks]
Oh, well..
Then who just went, "woof."
I went, "ruff."
I don't think so.
Who's this?
Michelle, you told a lie.
Yes, I did.
Look, sweetheart, it's not
very nice to tell lies.
I'm sorry.
I love the doggy.
Yeah, well, I don't.
Doggy, come back.
Michelle, we don't want
a dog livin' in the house.
- Yes, we do.
- No, we don't.
Yes, we do.
Aw.
My leopard underwear!
That's why we don't.
Hey, get that..
That's my favorite pair, you..
Run, doggy. Run, doggy!
And another thing about our
friend is her name is Minnie.
- Isn't that a nice name, dad?
- That's a lovely name.
Is your new friend a mouse?
No, but you're getting warmer.
Oh!
Daddy, we'd like you
to meet Minnie.
We've met.
Oh, look, dad.
Minnie's crazy about you.
She loves to hug.
This is your kind of dog.
My kind of dog is
on a bun with mustard.
Joey said if nobody wants her,
we can keep her.
Why on earth
would Joey say that
without talking
to me first, Joey?
Well, she wandered
into the backyard
we shared a sandwich
and, well, look at that face.
- She's so cute.
- Yeah, sure, she's cute to you.
You-you don't have doggy slobber
all over your pillow.
- Danny, get rid of the mutt.
- Can't we keep Minnie, please?
- Please?
[whimpering]
People, don't be fooled
by that look of innocence.
Underneath is a jungle beast
just thinking
"Here's a nice clean house
that I can totally destroy."
Trust me, that thing is gonna
track mud into the house
it's gonna chew everything up
and they're very
difficult to house train.
So was Michelle,
but we kept her.
I'm sorry, but I do not
want a dog in this house.
That's right.
And what Danny says, goes.
He's the boss and that's
the way things work and that's..
When did I become
your faithful sidekick?
[whimpering]
Something's wrong with Minnie.
(D.J.)
'Uh-oh, her tummy's fat,
and she's panting heavy.'
Kimmy's dog acted
the same way
right before she had puppies.
She's gonna have puppies
in my living room?
I'm gonna be an aunt!
Yes!
I'll go call Kimmy.
I don't know what..
[instrumental music]
This dog is in labor.
- Danny, do somethin'.
- Why me?
'Cause you're the only one
who had kids.
Not in the living room.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Minnie's having puppies.
[gasps]
No!
Thank you, Mrs. Gibbler.
Okay, Kimmy's mom
told me what we need.
Dad, here's the number
of the Gibbler's vet.
Joey, you go find something for
Minnie to have her puppies in.
Stephanie, you and I will go
get blankets and newspapers.
And I'm gonna go study
for my driving test.
What does that have
to do with Minnie?
'Cause if I
don't pass that test
I'm gonna need her puppies
to pull my sled around town.
[instrumental music]
[upbeat music over radio]
What are you doing?
Uh, studying for
my driver's test.
Is this how you
studied last time?
No, this time I got the book.
D.J., I feel like
I'm in high school again.
I was never any good
at studying for tests.
Probably 'cause
of the way you study.
What's the matter
with the way I study?
Nothing, if you're taking
a test on sink drumming.
- First of all, no music.
- No music?
- And no food.
- No chicken?
And finally,
sit in the chair..
...with this book.
There's nothing left
to do but study.
See, you're getting
smarter already.
- You guys missed it!
- What, Minnie had her puppies?
No, she sat up in her box
and went, "Where's my water?"
Get out!
[whimpering]
When something real happens,
let me know.
[growling]
Come on, Uncle Jesse,
I'll help you learn this stuff.
Thanks. That's
very nice of you.
Hey, you need your license
and I need a ride
to the mall tomorrow.
- Alright, let's do it.
- Okay.
Puppy update.
I called the animal shelter.
Nobody reported Minnie lost yet
but we'll keep trying
to find her owner.
Daddy, how did Minnie
make her puppies?
Well, sweetheart
I was hoping you'd
ask me that.
Remember when we talked about
how it takes a mommy
and a daddy to make a baby?
Yeah.
Well, it takes a mommy dog
and a daddy dog
to make a puppy dog.
Oh, thanks.
I'm always happy
to answer your questions.
Good, because
I have another one.
Oh-ho, goody gumdrops.
How do you think
Minnie met her husband?
I like that question.
Steph, some time ago
in a far away land
called Ohio..
...Minnie was taking a little
walk by the fire station.
And the firehouse dog, Arnie,
he took one look at Minnie
and he went "Bow wow wow."
It was love at first sniff.
'And then on one special day'
Arnie got down on three knees..
...and he said,
"Minnie, marry me.
You make my tail wag."
That was so romantic.
Daddy, how do you
know all this stuff?
Well, I'm your dad,
so I know everything.
And when I don't know,
I make up.
- I thought so.
- Come here.
[Michelle panting]
Well, it looks like
Minnie found a Lamaze coach.
Hey, everybody, I think
something's gonna happen.
- What's going on?
- What?
Hey, get in the box.
Get in the box.
Not you.
You better not be going
where I think you're going.
Stop! Heel! Sit!
Not on my bed, huh?
Danny, do somethin' about this.
This is not my fault.
Joey let the dog in the house
and it got the girls
all worked up.
Hey, if you weren't
such a neat freak
we would've already had a dog
that would've
chased this dog away.
Dad, we'll clean up
after Minnie.
You'll never know she's here.
I'll know she's here.
She's having puppies on my bed.
You don't know
how lucky you are.
Lucky to have puppies on my bed?
[indistinct chatter]
Wait, wait, wait, stop, stop.
Here comes a puppy.
Whoa, baby!
This is the most amazing thing
that's ever happened in my bed.
(Stephanie)
'Look, she's cleaning off
the puppy.'
How does she know what to do?
Well, it's part
of nature, Steph.
Nature is so awesome.
I can't believe
we were just fightin'
about Minnie having puppies.
This is so beautiful.
It all makes you think about
what's really important
in life, doesn't it?
Yeah, like being able
to share this moment
with people
you really love.
(D.J.)
'Ah, this is so incredible.'
Yesterday these puppies
weren't even here
and now they are.
And seeing them being born..
...it's like watching a miracle.
I'm so glad
you girls could see this.
Now maybe you can understand
how I felt the day
each of you were born.
My three little miracles.
- How cute.
- It's so little.
Yeah, they're tiny.
Why'd you pick my bed?
Can you watch
the drooling, please?
[instrumental music]
[vacuum cleaner whirring]
Oh, man, I've got enough fur
in this thing
to build another dog.
Minnie's owner just showed up.
He's here.
I'm sorry, girls.
It's time to
bring in the troops.
- 'Come on, Minnie.'
- 'Here we go, puppies.'
(Joey)
'Okay.'
We got bachelor number one.
Aw, look, oh,
bachelor number two.
Okay, bachelor number three
is right here.
Bachelor number four. Hi.
Look what I just
found in my bed.
A four-legged ankle-biter.
Uh, hi, I-I'm Frank Flood.
Minnie! Minnie.
Oh, Minnie.
Come over here.
Give me a kiss. Oh.
Thank you for taking
such good care of Minnie
and her puppies.
She was really lucky
to find such nice people.
Well, we were really lucky
to find such a sweet dog.
She sheds like crazy but..
...I guess that's not
really her fault, huh?
Truth is, if you
hadn't come to claim her
we probably would've
kept them all right here.
Oh, I can't wait to get
those little guys home.
I'll never, ever,
ever, ever forget you.
Bye, Minnie.
Say, uh, Frank, uh..
...would you mind
if I drive the girls over
once in a while
to visit the puppies.
I'll tell you what.
How would you like to keep
one of Minnie's puppies?
Would we? Could we?
Yeah, dad, can we?
You guys know
how I feel about dogs.
You just said you wouldn't
mind keeping all of them.
Well, that was when I thought
the dogs were leaving.
We promise
we'll take care of it.
Come on, Danny. I've wanted
a dog my whole life.
Oh, look at that face.
Danny, be strong.
Think dirt.
I can't help it, I'm wimping.
Look at that face.
Alright, we can have a puppy.
(in unison)
Yeah!
- Thank you.
- Hooray.
Michelle, you pick
the puppy.
I love this puppy!
The one that likes my bed?
- Okay.
- Here's a new addition.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Thank you for coming, Frank.
Thanks for all your help.
Are you kidding?
It was our pleasure.
- You got one?
- Yeah, I got one.
Okay. Go, baby. Okay.
Okay, hold on.
[instrumental music]
[theme music]